EKİNSU BOZDAĞ

Objective:

I'm a 27 years old game developer. I graduated from Bilkent University Computer Science in 2019. I am currently working for a mobile game company. I have 3 years of experience in hyper-casual, hybrid-casual mobile games. My ultimate aim is to try myself in various areas in mobile gaming.

Portfolio: https://ekinsubozdag.github.io/Portfolio



EDUCATION

Bilkent University, Ankara

B.S. in Computer Engineering Department

Graduate in May 2019

Ankara Atatürk Lisesi, Ankara

EXPERIENCE

Udo Games Ankara

Game Developer (11/2021 - 08/2022)

Game Developing for Hyper-Casual, Hybrid-Casual with Unity and C#

Lumos Games Remote

Game Developer (03/2021 - 11/2021)

Game Developing for Hyper-Casual with Unity and C#

Creasaur Entertainment Co. Ankara, Cyber Park

Game Developer (11/2019 - 03/2021)

Game Developing for Hyper-Casual with Unity and C#

Kuixo,Inc. Ankara,CyberPark

Game Developer Intern (07/2018 - 08/2018)

Game Developing for mobile with Unity and C#

Skills

Computer Skills: Unity, C#,Git

Personal Skills: Creative, Motivated,

Sporty, Gamer

Interests

Fitness, Volleyball, Games, Yoga

Achievements

2019 Bilkent University CS Fair -

Deeplay Marketing Award

Languages

Turkish(Native),

English(Advanced)

Address: Çankaya/Ankara (+90) 554 811 6061 ekinzu09@gmail.com